Hey Saiya has bought mine too, it cost a total of 22
thousand and in this 90 percent will be given
back to the companies, so guys welcome to my
new block, so we will see, you guys will get to know what the
video is going to be about, so
after camping our exams were
over, so that day I had to come home, so
this happened on this date and my
friends stopped me and said that you should go after the rain, if the
rain subsides then you can go, but I was
thinking that the rain ends in Lonavala,
so you guys know the
weather of that Amla, I left for home and
suddenly around the career, my bike
slid and the entire bike fell and I got
hurt, my hands and legs got bruised and the bike has got a
lot of damage, I don't know what is in front
or what is a stone, I don't know, the
bike slid because of the rain I was
not able to see anything in the helmet, I do
n't stay on the bike from the front, so I could
not see anything in the helmet and the bike slid, the
speed of the bike would be around 80 or 90, one should not
know in that, one should not ride the bike in the
form of a bike while going home  While going, he had exceeded the
speed, so I want to tell you people that
you should wear a helmet, no matter what happens, apply the speed limit
and in the rain, you should ride the bike properly, that is,
maintain a speed of 50-60, otherwise,
I have come here to
take delivery of the bike, I had
given it here on 30th July, probably, and
after a month, after making the insurance claim, I am
getting the bike now, so while making the
insurance claim, first they
take an advance from you, it will also be
around 40% of it, and after that, you will
pay the entire bill, then after that,
they will return the entire money to you in your bank account through cancellation, the
bill is paid, after that I will show all the bills and I will
show you where all its parts were
damaged, so finally,
after a month, my car has come to us,
and in this, I will tell you where all the parts were
damaged, so I have also brought mine,
it cost a total of 22 thousand and in this,
90% will also be returned to the companies, whatever
their charges are, by doing that and by doing that, the
chain charges, meaning  I assured you that
this Ganesha will get his money back at 90 percent.
I will tell you and
show you what all was broken in it.
When these guides were broken,
I was not looking at myself as to how much
damage I had suffered, where had my bike gone?
You must be a writer, so you can understand
that you love your bike so much, you do
n't think about yourself, you
think about your brother, how much pain he is going through,
so I was not
looking at myself before that. I was first looking at the bike, how much
damage it had caused, everything that is
special to me, when I had an
accident, those people had picked it up,
look at them first, even then I would
not give myself up, so I was looking at the bike, so I could
understand how much
love they have for it, so now I will
show you how much time it would take to get it back if the damage had happened
and this thing is not complete. It had
fallen on the left side,
it got completely changed and in this it was completely
broken, it got completely changed
and it was broken on the left side.  The
side is the
entire fairing has been changed, it has been completely changed
and coming to the front, there was
some damage here,
in this position it has been changed,
you must be seeing that it is not fitting at all
and this ring here was also broken, so
this has also been changed and you know that it is so
weak, if there is a little shock
then it opens completely, so this has been changed
and the clutch which is there had come down, so
clean sweep it has been completely changed, its
handle had come out, it has not been fitted inside yet,
they have it in stock,
when the order comes, they will
return it and its entire mirror has been changed,
here the entire stretch had come out
and so this entire mirror has been changed
and later they told that this light of
yours is completely damaged from inside, so
they changed the light completely, the light is
not fitted completely and there was a lot of noise in the engine,
they said that some Chinese
part was broken, so I changed it, it will be
completely new only and I will
not pay money to the companies in that, meaning overall
friends that you  So on the left side the entire
spare part has been changed, the headlight and the
oil of the vehicle has been changed and apart from that nothing else,
friend the total time is 22 thousand
so I thought that it should become a spectacle, there are only a few
parts of it and I will
put the photo of all the dinner parties, you guys can
see where it was, how much was the time,
how much was the price, so this is its complete
bill, you guys can see that the total amount made in the bill is 22
thousand 659 rupees, so
we will get 90% of it, that means
excluding their servicing which is 18 ₹100 550
and what else is added to it and there is something in China - so in
around 20 thousand you will get 90%,
so let's see how much money the companies
give, that much is not available
[Music] Turn it on
till today,
add fuel,
frustrated rear,
so the waiting period is quite long
if there is even a little damage, that means 12
part time job, so do not put it insured, pay
some money and get it done, if you
use French and MS Word then it will take a lot of time
So if you take the insurance then it will take about
a month, it is better to
go for a walk, if there are one or two parts then you can get
them repaired by paying money, now I am in the
mood to buy a new scooter, so you
guys please suggest which scooter should I buy right now, it is
running well, some things are coming to my mind too
and you guys tell me by commenting which
scooter should I buy and which should not and if you
like the video then like, share and
subscribe, see you next video